Guide to the Division of Nutritional Sciences records,1947-2018.
Division of Nutritional Sciences records
- Series XIII. Scholarships/Awards
  - Helen Gifft Fellowship, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lydia Lueder Darling Scholarship, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Katharina Wyckoff Harris Fellowship, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Cliff and Jane Carpenter Memorial Fund, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Margaret Newell Mitchell Fellowship, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Endowment to Support Graduate Student Research in Nutrition, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Flora Rose Graduate Scholarship; Orilla Wright Butts Fellowship; Flemmie Kittrell Fellowship, 2004; 2005; 2005 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Maynard Memorial Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - DNS Fellowships, 1987-1997 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - PhD Degrees Awarded and Faculty Honors and Awards - Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Series XIV. University Concerns
  - Admissions Data, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Corporate Liaison Group Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - University Concerns, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - University Concerns, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Rhodes Hall Space Issues, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Transition to Day Hall, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Transition to Day Hall, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Series XV. Photographs and Slides
  - Film Library in Roberts Hall- List of Nutrition Films, 1960, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Groton Survey, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Farm and Home Week, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Biochemistry of the Eye and Coprophagy, 1950-1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Food Science - Milk Vending, 1950-1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Metabolic Ward and Metabolic Diet Table, 1950-1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Metabolic Studies, 1950-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Savage Hall - Early Photos, 1940-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Savage Hall - Photos, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Savage Hall Photos-People (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Savage Hall New Photos, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Savage Hall New Photos, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Savage Hall New Photos, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Savage Hall Photos, Post 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Seminar Groups Faculty, 1940-1959 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Soybeans and Glucose Study, 1950,1954 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Vitamin C, 1950-1959 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lab Shots, 1950-1960 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lab Shots, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Lab Shots, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - DNS Lab Students Lab Shots, 1980 and 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Lab Shots - Clinical, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Staff Non-Academic (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Nutritional Biochemistry, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Visitor's Photos, Jane Goodall, Mrs. Cuomo (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - International Photos- Agathe Pellerin, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Thierry Brun's Black and white Negatives and Explanation (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Studies and Projects, 1940-1959 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - International Projects, 1950-1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Food Science and Nutrition Photos, 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Graduate Students Photos (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Photos-Unimal and Cornell Photos (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Students, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 30-33)
  - Graduate Students, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 34-40)
  - Graduate Students, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 41-45)
  - Graduate Students, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 46-52)
  - Senior Picnics, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - DNS External Review Team, 1979, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Retreat, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Retreat, 2008, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - WHO Training - Summer Session, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Slide Set - Parents and Preschoolers: A Recipe for Good Nutrition, no date (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Slides - Planning a Menu - By Dawn Treadwell, 1970-1979 (Box 20)